ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dubinsky, David. Early Photos and Individual (see also: Bx. 49 ff 11) [folder 1 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 16)
  includes: David Dubinsky speaking, present are: Julius Hochman, LaGuardia, Judge Jacob Panken, and Antonini; individual shots and portraits of David Dubinsky; Postcard of Sculpture dedicated to David Dubinsky
- Dubinsky, David. Early Photos and Individual (see also: Bx. 49 ff 11) [folder 2 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Dubinsky, David. Early Photos and Individual (see also: Bx. 49 ff 11) [folder 3 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Dubinsky, David. Early Photos and Individual (see also: Bx. 49 ff 11) [folder 4 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Dubinsky, David. Israel [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 20)
  includes: David Dubinsky with President Zalman Shazar; David Dubinsky with Prime Minister Levy Eshkol and Treasurer of the Histadrut - Yehoshua Levy; David Dubinsky with Golda Meir; David Dubinsky visiting Afro-Asian Institute; David Dubinsky in Wear Factory "Lahav"; David Stadium, a stadium dedicated to David Dubinsky in Haifa, Israel; Shop Scene in Israel Garment Factory
- Dubinsky, David. Israel [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Dubinsky, David. Later Years (Box 8, Folder 22)
  includes: photos of David Dubinsky at banquet; individual photos of David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky in Temple (Jewish); David Dubinsky with Rabbi
- Dubinsky, David. White House (see also: Bx. 49 ff 12) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  includes: Photos of David Dubinsky preparing for White House dinner; David Dubinsky at White House - Potofsky and others present; David Dubinsky testifying before a House Labor Subcommittee in response to charges of racial discrimination in the ILGWU; David Dubinsky and wife before White House dinner
- Dubrow, Evelyn (Box 8, Folder 24)
  includes: speech by Dubrow; Dubrow speaking before a committee; Dubrow with a man
- Eastern Out-of-Town [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 25)
  includes: small demonstration with placards - "Look, Our Eyes are Open. Want the Union"; Harry Wander presenting David Dubinsky with a check for child adoption, November 5, 1948; Connors - Chairman of Cerebral Palsy; Putterman - Chair Board of Directors CP, Nick Pimpinelli - Chairman Local 130, Sam Gross Chair Entertainment Committee Local 130, and Resigno - Chairman Welfare Committee Local 130: standing in front of billboard trying to entice people to give to Cerebral Palsy; Teamster bodyguard restrained from attacking an ILGWU picketer; Local 220 Christmas party; strike turned to violence, with police intervention
- Eastern Out-of-Town [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 26)
- East River Housing Corporation (Box 8, Folder 27)
  includes: David Dubinsky at Ground breaking ceremony for the East River Housing Corporation; $20,000,000 Mortgage Loan press conference - September 26, 1956; Art class painting, after 1956
- Education - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 28)
  includes: Local 91 English class for Spanish speaking workers; Speech by David Dubinsky discussing workers education at luncheon of students and teachers, April 10, 1937; women speaking to a classroom of women; Education Department visit to Radio City, Feb. 2, 1935; David Dubinsky, Dr. Drees, and Mark Starr Educational Director; Group Photo - Local 89 Basketball Team; Union hall during lunch - men playing chess; Educational Department field trip, preparing to leave for the Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1935; Visit to Museum of Science and Industry - NYC; English class to Spanish speaking workers; Classroom photos; At exhibit - Local 25 shows social dancing; Julius Hochman speaking to a class
- Education - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 1 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 1)
  includes: Nancy Adams, British Trade union congress officer and Pauline Newman reading book on David Dubinsky; University of Wisconsin Summer School for Workers, 1955; Zimmerman handing books to women in uniforms; meeting of Educational Committee; Siems speech at rally; Local 22 meeting; Starr with visiting Yugoslav delegation at meeting; Larry Rogan speaking to a class; classroom scenes; June 1958 Art Exhibit; David Dubinsky and LaGuardia; Educational Department visit to Museum of Science and Industry - NYC; Class in Trade Unionism - Current Events; Local 91 Art Class; Dr. Berio addressing delegates at a seminar; Educational Department visit to Museum of Natural History; Women at "School for Workers" at University of Wisconsin; Fashion Art class; Art classes in sculpting and painting; Art exhibit - Julius Hochman receiving a bust of himself; exhibit of plastic buttons at Cooper Union, NYC; Dress designing class; Musical revue benefit concert; International telegraphic bowling contest - scores reported to LA Joint Board; Upholstery class; Broodus Mitchell speech at Local 22 Educational Conference; Local 22 cast members of Pins and Needles present Manager Immerman with books for Local's library; Kansas City Joint Board Childrens' Dance Recital; Mandolin Orchestra, 1934; Lecture by Lew Hacker Dean of General Studies at Columbia University, and Fannia Cohn; Gomberg talking to French Delegation; speech by Julius Hochman; Miss ILGWU Contest; Southern Educational Conference Bathing Beauties, 1952; Maida Springer Kemp and guests; Mark Starr with Japanese industrialists; ILGWU display in France; Mark Starr and R. Lann, President of the Transportation Workers of Holland; "Learn To Vote" display to educate workers as to their voting privileges and those procedures; Boston Children's Choir
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 2 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 3 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 4 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 5 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 6 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 7 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 8 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 9 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Education (see also: 5780/049 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) [folder 10 of 10] (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Education and Recreation - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  includes: Fannia Cohn signing document; Adlai Stevenson speech; Local 89 Baseball Team; Local 149 Baseball team (1936); Local 160 Men and Women Basketball Teams (1936-37); Local 152 Boys and Girls Basketball Teams (1937); Local 10 Basketball team with trophy
- Education and Recreation - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Education and Recreation [folder 1 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 13)
  includes: Group photos of Local basketball (men and women) teams and men's baseball and soccer teams; action photo of man sliding into home in a baseball game, soccer game in progress; Local 105 Dance; men and women playing tennis; men playing basketball; Spring Festival - Spanish section; men playing checkers; men playing poker; women swimmers; men and women bowling; women doing gymnastics and aerobics; men climbing a rope; Jerome Richard - Boxer; men and women roller-skating
- Education and Recreation [folder 2 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Education and Recreation [folder 3 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Education and Recreation [folder 4 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Education and Recreation [folder 5 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Education and Recreation [folder 6 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Education and Recreation [folder 7 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Education and Recreation [folder 8 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Education and Recreation [folder 9 of 9] (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Education Classes - selected (Box 9, Folder 22)
  includes: Local 60 Educational Meeting, Harlem, NY, April 1934; Local 145 Class in Trade Unionism, Passaic, NJ, Jan. 21, 1935; Speech by Eleanor Roosevelt, Rose Pesotta present; Educational Meeting, Corona, Long Island, Feb. 5, 1935; Poster: "Our Union Pioneers Bringing Education, Recreation, Art and Medical Science to the Service of Labor"; Local 161 Chorus, Paterson, NJ; Local 62 Class in Labor Problems, Feb. 11, 1935; Local 144 Class in Trade Unionism, Newark, NJ, January, 1935; Mandolin Orchestra, Local 148, Union City, NJ, September 1934; Local 126 Hammonton NJ celebrating victory presenting the play "All for One" Oct. 27, 1934, "In Union there is Strength" New York, January 1935 by ILGWU Players, theatrical performance
- Education Classes (Box 10, Folder 1)
  includes: Local 32 - meetings; Spanish Dancers Emily Florez and Jose Lopez, Kansas City, Missouri, 1953; Local 91 Educational Meeting; Local 143 Educational Meeting, Yonkers, NY; Kansas City Joint Board Children's Dance Recital, doing "Walking in the Rain"; Art Exhibit, Kansas City, MO; School for Workers, University of Wisconsin, Summer of 1967; 1951 Art Class, Kansas City, MO
- Educational Miscellaneous - selected (Box 10, Folder 2)
  includes: Group Photo - Local 161, Paterson, NJ, Celebrating Beginning of the Educational Season, Feb. 15, 1935; Local 91, NYC. Class in Social Interpretation of Literature; Educational Department visit to Museum of Natural History, NYC., Jan 26, 1935; Local 143, Mt. Vernon, NY, Jan. 22, 1935, Class in Trade Unionism; Child Performance - "From Tots to Teens"; Group Photo of Educational Dept. in front of Radio City; Chorus of Bridgeport, Conn.
- Educational Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  includes: David Dubinsky, Fania Cohn and others celebrating; Japanese visitors viewing mural depicting history of the ILGWU; Class in the History of the American Labor Movement; Local 142 Booth at St. Louis Union Label Exposition; C. Zimmerman accepting painting of worker at sewing machine; Choir singing at banquet; At London School - Mayor Wagner, David Dubinsky; Julius Hochman speaking to a French Women's Study Group of Workers on Industry and Commerce; Button exhibit at Cooper Union; Harry Uviller speaking to a committee; at Needle Trade High School, speech to class by Principal Mortimer C. Ritter; Group Photo - Children from Israel; Mark Starr, hosting Mr. Masami Aizawa, Director of the Obihiro Citizen's Public Hall, and Mrs. Asa Tokunaga, President of the PTA Federation in Yokosuka, Japan; Min Lurye speaks to Officer Qualification class; College Summer Service Groups looking at Financial statement that had just recently been made public; Mark - Starr and Gus Tyler speech to NE Dept. Educational Conference - Dec. 13, 1957; Local 38 Meeting; Parade for President Lyndon B. Johnson; Banquet entertainment; Local 62 Chorus; Banquet photos; Milwaukee members boating on Lake Mendota; May 1960 - Andy Kline, President of Local 93, preparing the Reading Dancers for their routine for the 1960 ILG Benefit Show; Cocktail party at the Statler Hotel in St. Louis introducing the new Union Label to St. Louis retailers
- Educational Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Educational Miscellaneous [folder 3 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Einstein, Albert (Box 10, Folder 6)
  includes: Group Photo including Julius Hochman and Albert Einstein; Vladeck, Einstein and David Dubinsky
- Eisenhower, Dwight D. (see also: Bx. 49 ff 13) (Box 10, Folder 7)
  includes: Group Photo at White House Press Conference - James Mitchell, George Harrison, James Carey, David Dubinsky, David McDonald, President Eisenhower, George Meany, Walter Reuther, Harry Bates and William Schnitzler; David Dubinsky standing next to Eisenhower, Meany, Potofsky, Schnitzler, Mitchell present; Portrait of Eisenhower
- Elections - Union - selected (Box 10, Folder 8)
  includes: Waist and Dress Industry Workers voting on agreement - Women Voting in August, 1913
- Elections - Union (Box 10, Folder 9)
  includes: men and women voting at Union Hall; David Dubinsky Voting in 1953 election; Vote to end Garment Strike - Feb. 21, 1923
- Erlich - Alter - selected (Box 10, Folder 10)
  includes: Portraits of Henryk Erlich and Victor Alter
- Erlich - Alter (see also: Bx. 49 ff 14) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  includes: Erlich and Alter Meeting and Memorial Dedication by Jewish Labor Committee - David Dubinsky, William Green, George Meany; 1966 Press Conference on their behalf called upon the Soviet government to release all the facts concerning the tragedy
- Equal Rights - Selected (Box 10, Folder 11a)
- Equal Rights (Box 10, Folder 12)
  includes: Western Pennsylvania District Council women marching for equal rights for women
- Farm Workers (Box 10, Folder 13)
  includes: demonstration with placards - hotel workers supporting Grape Workers struggle; Minimum wage Demonstrators lined up in front of buses ready to picket; at League for Industrial Democracy Press Conference - Ceasar Chavez, Charles Zimmerman; Individual shot of Chavez
- Fashion Institute (Box 10, Folder 14)
  includes: Meeting regarding David Dubinsky Student Center - David Dubinsky, Zimmerman; Ground Breaking Ceremony - F.I.T. - David Dubinsky Student Center, April 21, 1969 - Manhattan Borough President Percy Sutton, David Dubinsky, Louis Stulberg, Mayor John Lindsay and Chair of the Fashion Institute of Technology David Zelinka present; David Dubinsky looking at model of the David Dubinsky Student Center with Henoch Mendelsund of NY Cloak Joint Board, President of Lord and Taylor Melvin Dawley, and Head of Jonathan Logan Inc. David Schwartz; Speech by David Dubinsky at the David Dubinsky Student Center; Photo of David Dubinsky in front of the David Dubinsky Student Center, with Sol Chaikin speaking with a woman
- Federation of Union Representatives (Box 10, Folder 15)
  includes: "Members of 'Union Within the Union' Picketing in front of the ILGWU" with signs protesting Anti-Union activity; Federation of Union Representatives marching in 1961 Labor Day Parade; David Dubinsky speaking with Federation of Union Representatives tossing bundles of anti-ILGWU leaflets out of a nearby building covering David Dubinsky and reporters
- Feinberg, Israel (Box 10, Folder 16)
  includes: October 21, 1946 - Farewell Luncheon to Feinberg - Frederick Umhey, Matthew Woll, David Dubinsky, and Israel Feinberg
- Fire Wardens and Program [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 17)
  includes: Memorial service for workers who perished in the Monarch Undergarment Fire, March 19, 1958/Proposed initiation of Shop Fire Wardens to work with NY Fire Department to insure safety through fire prevention; ILGWU Fire Wardens marching in Parade with New York Fire Department; David Dubinsky receiving a Certificate of Appreciation from Edward Thompson, New York City Fire Chief in honor of the ILGWU Fire Warden Program; NYC Fire Commissioner Edward Cavanagh conversing with Josephine Nicolosi - Triangle Fire (1911) Survivor, and Carmen Torres - Monarch Fire Survivor in City Council Chambers, also present is Leon Stein, editor of JUSTICE
- Fire Wardens and Program [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Firms - Selected (Box 10, Folder 18a)
- Firms [folder1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 19)
  includes: Ribbon Cutting at Russ Togs; Shop scene including Meany and David Dubinsky; Signing of Majestic Agreement, February 13, 1962; Speech by David Dubinsky at banquet, Eleanor Roosevelt on Dais; David Dubinsky speaking to a group of people; David Marmolstern Tribute Luncheon - included are David Dubinsky and Julius Hochman; Women walking across a street in "Chain Gang" form, with prison fatigues and connected by a chain; Signing of an agreement at City Hall - Mayor Wagner and David Dubinsky present; David Dubinsky in shop scene; Little League Baseball Player protesting imported Baseball equipment with a sign "Baseball. The Great Un-American Game"; Opening of Barbizon Corporation Plant in Patterson, NJ - David Dubinsky in shop scene at the cutter
- Firms [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Florida (Box 10, Folder 21)
  includes: Dress Piece Rate Conference in Miami for the benefit of Locals 415 and 475; Secretary of Labor Willard Wirtz shaking hands with David Dubinsky in Miami Beach, March 1, 1966; Car with two signs - Picture of the Union Label and "Merry Christmas ILGWU Local 570, Sanford, Florida".
- Foreign, General Matters (Box 10, Folder 22)
  includes: Group Photos including David Dubinsky and Antonini in Rome; Shop Scene - 1980, Banako, Mali; David Dubinsky, Matthew Woll and their Wives leaving Queen Elizabeth; David Dubinsky, Meany, Green and George Harrison heading for London for a meeting by way of ship; three U.S. Delegates at the London Labour Conference - November 28, 1949 - Meany, Green, Woll; Dubinsky presentation of $100000 loan to Dutch Workers
- Foreign, South America [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 23)
  includes: George Meany and David Dubinsky autographing Meany's speech in Sao Paulo, Brazil, November 12-14, 1956; Speech by Meany at Sao Paulo, Brazil - 1956; Meany, Minister Richard Porter Buttrick, Consul General, David Dubinsky; Meany, Romualdi, Cavalcanti, Fava, and David Dubinsky present at luncheon where Meany's lapel is pinned by the President of the Food Workers Federation; Buenos Aires Press Conference - Meany and Romualdi present; David Dubinsky, Meany, Knight and Romualdi boarding plane leaving Brazil; Argentine Trade Unionists meeting; 1956 - David Dubinsky on Good Will Mission to Buenos Aires - Shop Scene, 1956; David Dubinsky Speech to Sao Paulo Labor Leaders. Forward - includes: David Dubinsky speaking at the 60th Anniversary of the Jewish Daily Forward Banquet; Photo of the Jewish Daily Forward Building. Gaitshell, Hugh - includes: 55th Jubilee Workmens' Circle, Carnegie Hall, May 20, 1956 - Gaitshell in many group photos, including David Dubinsky, Potofsky, Louis Munoz Marin, Antonini, Hochman; David Dubinsky and wife. General Executive Board - selected - includes: Executive Board Group Photo - 1965; 1971 Pre-convention Meeting: Louis Stulberg, Howard Molisani, JUSTICE Editor Leon Stein and Managing Editor Meyer Miller; Group Photo - General Executive Board 1947-1950; Group Photo - General Executive Board 1940-1942; General Executive Board 1934-1937 at a rally welcoming them. General Executive Board (see also: Bx. 49 ff 15) - includes: Group Photo - General Executive Board 1947-1950; General Exec. Board Meeting, March 1955; Stulberg welcoming Wilbur Daniels to the GEB, Molisani and Mendelsund present; GEB Meeting at Unity House included: James Lipsig, Edward Kramer, William Ross, Shelley Appleton, Samuel Otto, Luigi Antonini, Fred Siems, David Dubinsky, Matthew Schoenwald, Stulberg, Bernard Shane, Sol C. Chaikin, Lillian Weinberger, David Gingold, Gus Tyler, Angela Bombace, Murray Gross, Wilbur Daniels, Israel Breslow, Charles Zimmerman, Louis Nelson, Henoch Mendelsund, Howard Molisani, Philip Kramer, Moe Falikman, Sam Janis, Alberto Sanchez, Morris Bialis and Martin Morand; NY members of the General Executive Board 1909: Harry Kleinman, Sol Polakoff, B. Fris Lurasser, John A. Dyche, Abraham Rosenberg, Sam Shindler, and Julius Wolf; Meeting of the GEB marking the completion of Stulberg's first year as President.
- Foreign, South America [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 24)
- General Office - selected (Box 11, Folder 1)
  includes: International Headquarters - 1710 Broadway, New York City
- Gingold, David (Box 11, Folder 1a)
  includes: Portrait of Gingold
- Goldberg, Arthur - selected (Box 11, Folder 1b)
- Goldberg, Arthur (Box 11, Folder 2)
  includes: Goldberg and David Dubinsky walking on Atlantic City Boardwalk; David Dubinsky and Goldberg talking; May 1961, Atlantic City, Presentation to Goldberg an inscribed resolution commending his work and achievements; speech by Goldberg; Goldberg, David Dubinsky at Unity House, 1961; Goldberg arrival at Unity House, 1961, greeted by David Dubinsky
- Gompers - Selected (Box 11, Folder 2a)
- Gompers, Samuel (Box 11, Folder 3)
  includes: Gompers posing on Atlantic City Boardwalk, 1924; The meeting at which the strike was declared - Samuel Gompers speech to three thousand shirtwaist makers in the Cooper Union, New York, November 22, 1909
- Green, William - Selected (Box 11, Folder 3a)
- Green, William (see also: Bx. 49 ff 16) [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 4)
  includes: Green speaking with David Dubinsky; Green in David Dubinsky's office; Green and David Dubinsky at podium; Green Testimonial Dinner - August 8, 1940; David Dubinsky speech at Green's Testimonial Dinner; Portrait near time of death; Portrait of Green prior to his reign as President of the AF of L; Green presenting Julius Hochman with a menorah; David Dubinsky, Bevin and Green at London Conference, November 1949
- Green, William (see also: Bx. 49 ff 16) [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Greene, Sol (Box 11, Folder 6)
  includes: Charles Zimmerman and Sol Green with a bandage on his head, February, 1959
- Group Photos - Early - selected (Box 11, Folder 7)
  includes: Group Photo including David Dubinsky, Hochman, Antonini; Cloak, SK., Reefer Makers Union 1921-22, Information Committee; other posed group photos
- Group Photos - Early (see also: Bx. 49 ff 18) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  includes: Banquet scene including David Dubinsky; Morris Hillquit addressing the 1918 Convention - President Schlesinger, Secretary Baroff and members of the General Executive Board on platform; Group Photo, 1918 of "General Officers, Members of the General Executive Board, and Friends of Our Union"; David Dubinsky, Grossman, Sigman, and Harry Wander taking a boat trip circa 1924; Circa 1930 - at City Hall, New York City - Lieutenant Governor Lehman, acting Mayor McKee, H. Wander, L. Antonini, David Dubinsky, W. Blum, B. Schlesinger, J. Breslau, R. Ingersoll, J. Hochman, I. Nagler, Sam Perlmuster, I Spillman
- Group Photos - selected (Box 11, Folder 9)
  includes: Board of Officials Cloak Makers Union; Board of Trustees Retirement Fund, October 16, 1965, Hotel Astor, includes David Dubinsky, Antonini, Chaikin
- Group Photos (see also: Bx. 49 ff 17) [folder 1 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 10)
  includes: Chaikin, Zimmerman and David Dubinsky with bust of David Dubinsky; Thirty-first Convention, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1962; Sadie Reisch and Mary Goff Schuster at a demonstration; photo from the 1965 Convention; Photos from Chicago Building Dedication; General Executive Board Meeting, 1955; Meeting in Houston, Texas, Sept. 1950; Group Shot - George Price, Louis Stern, Charles Zimmerman, Dr. Lewis Miller, Isidore Nagler, Dr. Philip Hillkowitz, Morris Feinstone, Philip Kapp, Joseph Belsky, Jacob Miller, Joseph Schlossberg, Gustave Strebel, Pauline Newman, Adolph Germer, Abraham Snyder, Samuel Rosenthal, Harry Begoon, Rose Ash, E.M. Rokofsky, Charles Miller; David Dubinsky and Min Matheson, 1972; Photo of Minority Women; Passing of the Gavel from David Dubinsky to Stulberg
- Group Photos (see also: Bx. 49 ff 17) [folder 2 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Group Photos (see also: Bx. 49 ff 17) [folder 3 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Group Photos (see also: Bx. 49 ff 17) [folder 4 of 4] (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Group Photos - Officers and Staff - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 14)
  includes: General Executive Board, 1902; Banquet Photo - November 4, 1934; other posed group photos; Group Photo including David Dubinsky, Bernard Shane; Kreindler, Angela Bambace, David Dubinsky, Hannah Haskel; 1940 Convention Delegates
- Group Photos - Officers and Staff - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 14a)
- Group Photos - Officers and Staff [folder 1 of 2] (Box 11, Folder 15)